laneone.com 2019-05-07

# LaneOne Privacy Policy

#### LaneOne Privacy Policy

##### Last Updated: September 27th, 2018

Protecting your privacy is really important to us. Accordingly, we're providing this Privacy Policy to explain our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we receive when you use our Services (as defined in our Terms of Service, accessible at [www.laneone.com/terms](https://www.laneone.com/terms)). This Privacy Policy applies only to those websites, services and applications included within Services and doesn't apply to any third-party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible through our Services. Also, please note that, unless we define a term in this Privacy Policy, all capitalized words used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service. 

LaneOne reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new or updated privacy policy through the Services. We recommend that you review such Privacy Policy periodically for changes. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO FUTURE CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST STOP USING THE SERVICES AFTER THE EFFECTIVE DATE OF SUCH CHANGES. 

#### How do we collect and use information?

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, to administer your use of the Services (including your Account, if you are an Account holder), and to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate our Services. 

Account Information. When you create an Account we'll collect certain information that can be used to identify you, directly or indirectly, such as your name, phone number, and email address (Personally Identifiable Information or PII). When you purchase a ticket to a Paid Event, we'll collect other PII from you such as your shipping address. We may also collect certain information that is not PII because it cannot be used by itself to identify you, such as your zip code and the city in which you are located. We may use your PII to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the Opt-Out procedure described in this policy below. 

Information Collected Using Cookies. We collect certain information through the use of cookies, which are small text and/or image files (such as web beacons and pixel tags) that are saved by your browser when you access our Services. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to identify that you've logged in to the Services and to tell us how and when you interact with our Services. We may also use cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our Services and to customize and improve our Services. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted when you log off from the Services and close your browser. Although most browsers automatically accept cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies. Please note, however, that if you don't accept cookies, you may not be able to access all portions or features of the Services. We may engage third-party services providers (including third-party advertisers) that may also place their own cookies on your browser. By using the Services, you consent to our use of cookies and similar technologies. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of cookies and does not apply to use of cookies by such third parties. We use cookies to provide our services and improve your experience. Refer to our Cookie Policy for more info and ways to opt-out. 

Information Related to Use of the Services. Our servers automatically record certain information about how a person uses our Services (we refer to this information as Log Data), including both Account holders and non-Account holders (either, a User). Log Data may include information such as a User's Internet Protocol (IP) address, unique identifiers (such as mobile device identification numbers), browser type, operating system, the web page that a User visits before and after accessing our Services, the pages or features of our Services to which a User browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, Events on our Services which a User views, tags, or likes, search terms, the links on our Services that a User clicked on, information about a User’s interactions with e-mail messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were received, opened, or forwarded, standard server log information and other statistics. 

Location Information. When you use our App we collect and store information about where you are located, such as by converting your IP address into a rough geolocation and accessing your mobile devices' GPS coordinates or course location if you enable location services on your device. We may use location information to improve and personalize our Services for you. 

Advertising Identifiers. We collect a unique ad tracking identifier (the Advertising Identifier or "IDFA" on Apple devices and the Google Advertising ID or "AID" on Android devices) from your device. These identifiers are unique to your device, but you can reset them or limit their use through your device settings, as described in our Cookie Policy. These identifiers do not contain your name or email address. We use these ad tracking identifiers together with our analytics technologies in order to inform our targeted advertising initiatives. 

We use information collected through the Services to: (1) administer the Services and we analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) this information to improve and enhance the Services by expanding their features and functionality and tailoring them to our Users' needs and preferences; (2) provide you with the products, promotions, services, newsletters, and information you request and respond to correspondence that we receive from you; (3) contact you via email and otherwise about your account, products, services, contests, and events that we think might be of interest to you; (4) send you promotional material or special offers on our behalf or on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties; (5) provide, maintain, administer or expand the Services, perform business analyses, or for other internal purposes to improve the quality of our business, the Services, and other products and services we offer; (6) customize and personalize your use of the Services. We may use a person's IP address to fight spam, malware and identity theft. We also use the IP Address to generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how our Services are used. We may use your non-personal information (including personal information that has been de-identified and/or aggregated) for any reason at our sole discretion. 

#### What Information Do We Share With Third Parties?

We will not share any PII that we have collected from you except as described below: 

Information Shared with Our Services Providers. We may engage third party service providers to work with us to administer and provide the Services (e.g. we use third parties to process payments for purchases made via the Services). These third-party services providers have access to your PII only for the purpose of performing services on our behalf and are expressly obligated not to disclose or use your PII for any other purpose. 

Information Shared with Event Partners. We may share information with our Event partners, including a third party who provides, sponsors, or tickets an Event, such as Live Nation, Ticketmaster, an Event promoter, or record label, and the Venue where the Event is being held, to enable you to attend an Event (e.g. so that your ownership of the tickets can be verified by the Venue, or so that you can collect your ticket at the Venue's box office or will call, or so that your tickets or other Event information or merchandise can be emailed or shipped to you). Our Event partners have access to your PII for the purpose of performing services on your behalf. Additionally, and from time to time, Event Partners may send you informational, marketing and/or promotional communications that might be of interest to you and/or related to the Event. You may opt-out from Event Partners' communications at any time by following the unsubscribe link included with any of these communications. You should read their privacy policies to learn how they treat your information. 

Information Shared with Other Third Parties. We may share aggregated information and non-identifying information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other similar purposes. We may use Log Data to compile popularity charts and may share this with third parties. We may use third-parties to serve advertisements on the Services. These third parties may set their own cookies or similar web technologies to collect information about users’ online activities over time and across different websites. 

Information Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions. Information that we collect from our users, including PII, is considered to be a business asset. As a result, if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy or if we are acquired as a result of a transaction such as a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your PII may be disclosed or transferred to the third-party acquirer in connection with the transaction. 

Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others. It is our policy to protect you from having your privacy violated through abuse of the legal systems, whether by individuals, entities or government, and to contest claims that we believe to be invalid under applicable law. However, it is also our policy to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties. Accordingly, we reserve the right to disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary: (i) to satisfy or comply with any applicable law, regulation or legal process or to respond to lawful requests, including subpoenas, warrants or court orders; (ii) to protect our property, rights and safety and the rights, property and safety of third parties or the public in general; and (iii) to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. 

We may share non-personal information (including personal information that has been de-identified and/or aggregated), such as demographic and usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other third parties for any reason at our sole discretion. 

#### The Security of Your Information

We are very concerned with safeguarding your information and have adopted security procedures that we have determined are reasonable and appropriate, to help protect against loss, misuse, and unauthorized access to the information you provide to us. The security of your PII is important to us. But remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure and we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to the Services and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your information during transmission, for example, across the Internet. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted using 128-bit encryption. In some cases, we also encrypt sensitive information where it is stored on our systems. 

#### Links to Other Sites

Our Services may contain links to other websites and services. Any information that you provide on or to a third-party website or service is provided directly to the owner of the website or service and is subject to that party's privacy policy. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites or services and we're not responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of those websites or services. To protect your information, we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of other websites and services that you access. 

#### Social Networking Sites

We may work with certain third-party social media providers to offer you their social networking services through our Services. For example, you may be allowed to use third-party social networking services, including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, and others to share information about your experience on our Services with your friends and followers on those social networking services. These social networking services may be able to collect information about you, including your activity on our Services. These third-party social networking services also may notify your friends, both on our Services and on the social networking services themselves, that you are a user of our Services or about your use of our Services, in accordance with applicable law and their own privacy policies. If you choose to access or make use of third-party social networking services, we may receive information about you that you have made available to those social networking services, including information about your contacts on those social networking services. You also may be able to link an account from a social networking service (e.g., Facebook, Twitter) to an account through our Services. This may allow you to use your credentials from the other site or service to sign in to certain features on our Services. If you link your account from a third-party site or service, we may collect information from those third-party accounts, and any information that we collect will be governed by this Privacy Policy. 

#### Emailing and Messaging Via a LaneOne Account

As part of our Services, Account holders may communicate with LaneOne and/or other Account holders and, to a limited extent, with non-registered users, through use of their Accounts. Account holders may email or message non-registered users outside of the Services to share information regarding an Event, or to invite them to join or refer them to the Services. Additionally, Account holders can email or message other Account holders regarding an Event. 

You retain the rights to your copyrighted content or information that you submit to LaneOne, except as described below: 

By submitting content to LaneOne, you grant us a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive, unrestricted, worldwide license to reproduce, prepare derivative works, distribute copies, perform, or publicly display your content in any medium and for any purpose, including commercial purposes, and to authorize others to do so. We may, for example, display your comments as reviews on our website or elsewhere, or in our marketing, with or without attribution. 

#### Modifying Your Information

You can access and modify the PII associated with your Account through the Account Profile page on the Site or the App. If you want us to delete your PII and your Account, please contact us at privacy@laneone.com with your request. We'll take steps to delete your information as soon as is practicable, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law. 

#### Opting Out / Retention

We may use information that we collect from you to provide you with promotional emails, newsletter notifications, and notifications about upcoming Events that are likely to be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive promotional emails, newsletter notifications, Event notifications or reminders, or other communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or through the Services, or notify us at privacy@laneone.com. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you Services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

#### International Transfer

Your PII may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you're located outside the United States and choose to provide your PII to us, we may transfer your PII to the United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of any PII represents your agreement to that transfer. 

LaneOne is a company established in the US, and as such your data may be transmitted, stored, and/or processed in the United States. The United States of America is a country "outside of the EU that offers an adequate level of data protection" as determined by the European Commission per article 45 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (<https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-transfers-outside-eu/adequacy-protection-personal-data-non-eu-countries_en>) 

#### Our Policy Toward Children

Our Services are not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect PII from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected PII of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible. 

#### Stripe

We use Stripe for payment, analytics, and other business services. Stripe collects identifying information about the devices that connect to its services. Stripe uses this information to operate and improve the services it provides to us, including for fraud detection. You can learn more about Stripe and read its privacy policy. 

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

Any information that we collect is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, modify and revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we'll notify you of such changes by posting them on the Services or by sending you an email or other notification, and we'll indicate when such changes will become effective. 

#### Questions?

Please contact us at [privacy@laneone.com](mailto:privacy@laneone.com) if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy.
